Max Wiggedal

I am a Full Stack Developer with knowledge of a wide range of programming languages. I can build both backend and frontend applications, and manage the whole process on my own. I have a strong technical ability and I also have experience in cloud environments.

Phone +46 0704436475

Email

contact@maxwiggedal.dev

Website

https://maxwiggedal.dev/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cypoint Inspire AB — Consult/Software Engineer

OCTOBER 2022 - PRESENT

Working on a product information management system called Inriver, I create extensions and templates to allow the customer to more easily enrich their products. I also communicate with customers and partners to provide status updates as well as input on progression.

Northwood Studios — System Administrator/Web Developer

MARCH 2019 - AUGUST 2022

Worked on internal tools, APIs, and server infrastructure. While working here I gained experience using C#, PHP, Redis and MySQL. I also gained experience in deploying to a production environment using continuous integration and continuous deployment practices.

EDUCATION

Rodengymnasiet, Norrtälje — Information Technology

AUGUST 2019 - JUNE 2022

PROJECTS

The Universe Network

A Minecraft server of 5k members that focuses on competitive play and building an active social hub where players can interact with each other. I helped create a majority of the infrastructure and networking code.

Portfolio

A portfolio website created using NextJS and TailwindCSS. The website takes Search Engine Optimization into mind and provides information about me as well as projects I have worked on.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript

TypeScript

React

ASP.NET Core / C#

Git

MongoDB

MySQL

Redis

LANGUAGES

Swedish

English

Echelon Service SSO

A single-sign on application used to centralize user accounts into one place and authorize access to other applications by simply having one account on the single-sign on application.

Echelon Service

The core service for Echelon that provides a variety of administrative tools to the customer, the website targets the audience of certain online communities and is built using ASP.NET Core for the backend and the frontend using React.